<resources>
    <string name="app_name">SAHIT Score</string>

    <string name="open_message">Get Started!</string>
    <string name="region">Your region</string>
    <string name="email">Your email</string>

    <string name="title_activity_information">Information</string>
    <string name="definitions_text">
        "<b>Definitions</b>\n
        <i>Age</i> should be entered as the patient\'s age in years.\n\n
        <i>Hypertension</i> should be defined or considered present if there is a known history of
        hypertension, the patient was taking antihypertensive medications prior to admission or
        there are other clinically apparent signs consistent with essential hypertension such as
        very high blood pressure on admission or electrocardiogram, echocardiogram, kidney or
        other end-organ signs or laboratory findings consistent with a history of hypertension.\n\n
        <i>Neurological or clinical grade</i> of the patient is based on the grade when they are
        admitted to hospital and prior to aneurysm repair. This model includes studies that
        determined the neurological grade before aneurysm repair but before and after
        resuscitation including insertion of an external ventricular drain. Thus, you should use
        the neurological grade determined before aneurysm repair. The model uses the World
        Federation of Neurological Surgeons (WFNS) scale that is based on the modified Glasgow
        coma score and presence or absence of focal motor deficit (including aphasia) as outlined
        below.{Teasdale, 1988 #17556;Drake, 1988 #8208;Teasdale, 1974 #34155} If the Hunt and
        Hess system is used, an approximate conversion method is shown.{Hunt, 1968 #10458}\n\n
        <i>Size</i> is defined as the largest diameter of the aneurysm. This is usually the length from
        the aneurysm neck at the aneurysm origin from the parent artery to the end of the dome of
        the aneurysm.\n\n
        <i>Location</i> follows the ISAT categorization as such:\n
        ACA - Anterior cerebral artery, including Anterior communication, proximal to A comm,
        pericallosal.\n
        ICA - Internal carotid artery, including proximal to or ophthalmic region, posterior
        communication region, and the bifurcation.\n
        MCA - Middle cerebral artery.\n
        PCA - Posterior circulation artery, including vertebro-basilar artery and branches.\n\n
        <i>Fisher grade</i> should be calculated using the cranial computed tomographic scan obtained
        when the patient presented with subarachnoid hemorrhage and before aneurysm repair:\n
        1 - No SAH or intraventricular hemorrhage.\n
        2 - Diffuse deposition of thin layer with all vertical layers of blood (interhemispheric
        fissure, insular cistern, ambient cistern) &lt;1 mm thick.\n
        3 - Vertical layers of blood ≥1 mm thick or localized clots (clots defined as &gt;3 x 5
        mm).\n
        4 - Diffuse or no subarachnoid blood, but with intracerebral or intraventricular clots.\n\n
        <i>Method of repair</i> indicates whether the ruptured aneurysm was repaired by neurosurgical
        clipping, endovascular coiling or not repaired. The data from which this model is
        constructed leads to the recommendation that aneurysms repaired with adjunctive surgical
        methods in addition to clipping including bypass and trapping are classified as
        neurosurgical clipping and stent-assisted coiling, flow diverters and such are classified
        as endovascular coiling."
    </string>
    <string name="calc">Calculate</string>

    <string name="title_activity_input">Calculate</string>
    <string name="message1String">Prediction models for 3 month outcome after aSAH</string>
    <string name="message2String">Admission Characteristics</string>
    <string name="core">Core</string>
    <string name="ageString">Age (0–99)</string>
    <string-array name="hypertension">
        <item>[Hypertension]</item>
        <item>Yes</item>
        <item>No</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="wfnsGrades">
        <item>[WFNS Grade]</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
        <item>5</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="neuro">Neuro</string>
    <string name="sizeString">Size (mm)</string>
    <string-array name="locations">
        <item>[Location]</item>
        <item>ACA</item>
        <item>ICA</item>
        <item>MCA</item>
        <item>PCA</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="fisherGrades">
        <item>[Fisher Grade]</item>
        <item>1</item>
        <item>2</item>
        <item>3</item>
        <item>4</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="full">Full</string>
    <string-array name="repairMode">
        <item>[Repair Modality]</item>
        <item>Clip</item>
        <item>Coil</item>
        <item>Not Repaired</item>
    </string-array>
    <string name="clear">Clear</string>

    <string name="title_activity_results">Results</string>
    <string name="coreString">Core Characteristics</string>
    <string name="neuroString">Neuro Characteristics</string>
    <string name="fullString">Full Characteristics</string>

    <string name="mortality">With a 95&#37; confidence interval, the error for mortality is between&#160;</string>
    <string name="unfavourable">&#37; and for unfavourable outcome it is between&#160;</string>
    <string name="and">&#37; and&#160;</string>
    <string name="percent">%</string>

    <string name="home">Home</string>
</resources>
